DELIVERANCE TIME
Here is Wise Man Racine moving in the midst of the congregation
of The Synagogue Church Of All Nations during a typical Sunday Service.
As he prays, God uses the wise man as an instrument of deliverance
where there is bondage in the lives of the multitudes.
And the unclean spirits behind their problems are exposed and forced to come out.
Indeed, to know God's presence is to know God's power.
As Wise Man Racine continues to move in the midst of the congregation,
he prays for this lady who immediately falls to the ground under the superior power of God.
Let's see what happens in her, following an encounter with Wise Man Racine.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, you unclean spirit, come out of this body!
The spirit of credit, you cannot remove it.
Nobody!
For how long have you been tormenting her life?
Over 16 years. Nobody can do it.
Nobody!
How did you enter her life?
Through the bush.
Ancestral spirit - you cannot remove that spirit.
The spirit of credit - you cannot remove it.
My ears are blocked.
Please, my ears.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus' name, you are free.
Glory be to Jesus Christ, you heard the voice of the evil spirit
that it is the spirit of credit, and she has been delivered to the glory of God.
Thank You, Jesus!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Esse. I come from Warri (Nigeria).
I sell food.
I sell rice, fried rice, jollof rice, salad, chicken, ogwo, eba, egusi, ogbono.
Everything is sold at my store.
I sell the food but I don't see the money.
It's my own money I used to start the business.
As I sell, I don't see the money; all the money seems to vanish.
I told my sister that all my money had gone.
She said I should borrow money.
I started to borrow money.
I borrowed to sell food and the money vanished again.
My sister borrowed money for me.
She said she sells all sorts of food.
Whenever she sells food, she doesn't see the result of the products she's selling.
Instead she keeps on borrowing money,
to the extent that her sister also assisted her in borrowing money
in order to make up for the loss she had been making from selling food.
I borrowed money but I couldn't pay it back.
People would come to ask for their money and we would fight.
The father of my children does security work, earning N8,000 a month.
He said people were coming to fight with him,
so since he never paid my bride price, I should pack my things and go!
We've just heard from the woman.
She said in the course of selling the food stuff she had been cooking,
she had never made any gain from what she has been selling.
So she went about borrowing from here and there to the extent that
her sister also assisted her in borrowing money, in order to make up for the loss
of selling the food and not making any gains.
To the point that her husband called her one day and said,
"Look, I've not even paid for your dowry
and you go about borrowing money here and there.
You'd better carry your problem and see how you solve it
because I'm not ready to carry it for you".
One day he said he was going to work, took some of his things and ran away.
I was inside the house with my children.
All the people I owed would come and some would beat me.
One day I came out of the house.
A woman came to my store to buy food.
The woman said, "Oh, Mama Rice, don't you sell food anymore?"
I told her I owed debts from my head to my toes.
She said that to the extent that one day her husband just came in,
took some of his clothes, and absconded. He ran away from her.
Since then, those people she had borrowed money from would come.
They would beat, scold, molest her.
Then one day a woman met her and said,
"Look, Madam Rice, you've not been selling food again, why?"
She told the woman she'd been borrowing money here and there.
And the woman said, "Look, I've got a solution to your problem".
The woman gave me an address and said that she knew a man who helped people.
I said, "Okay, will you take me to him?"
She said she would not take me there but she wrote the address for me.
She said if I took the three children, he would solve my problem.
I said okay.
She said that if I took my children, the man would solve my problem.
I agreed.
I went there and knocked on the door. The gateman said I should enter.
I entered. I didn't sit down but stood there.
A man came out of a room.
He said before I came, they had already told him my problem.
I said, "Thank God!"
He said that a person uses what he has to solve his problem.
I said that if I had something, I would use it to solve my problem.
He said he wanted to buy this child for N400,000.
You've listened to the woman.
She said she met a lady who said she had a solution to her problem.
She said, no problem, she was ready to do it.
The lady then said, "When you are going to this place, I will not go with you.
I will give you the address, but make sure you take your three children along with you".
She went to the place. Immediately she got there, the security man opened the door for her.
When she went in, she met a man that said,
"Look, I already know your problem, and the only solution to your problem is
you give me one of your children for the sum of N400,000".
He said he would buy this kid and follow me to the bank to collect the money
I then said I would not be able to sell him.
I then walked out of the door.
He said, "Madam, think about it very well before you die in pain.
Those people will kill you".
When I got home, I thought about it.
My mind told me that I should just drop the child and leave.
She said after she met the man and he told her,
"Look, I'm going to buy one of your sons for N 400,000",
she left and the man said, "Look, you know your problem is so great.
You'd better think about it and come back to me so that your problem will be solved".
She said when she left the place, she started thinking about it,
"Why don't I just drop this child and get the money and solve my problem".
As I was thinking like that, a woman came. She used to sell garri to me.
When I didn't have money to pay, she would give food for me and my children to eat.
I told her that I was going to take this child and solve the problem.
The woman shouted and said, "Do you want to sell your own child?"
The money she had earned from selling garri that morning, she lent it to me.
She said I should use the money for transport and leave Warri immediately.
I told her that I would not be able to leave at that time
because the people I was owing would know I was running away.
She said that I should go to sleep like somebody who had not heard anything.
As the day was breaking, I woke up the children. I told them we were going to Lagos
but I didn't know where we were going in Lagos.
I said we were going to Lagos.
My daughter asked me, "Mommy, where are we going?"
I said, "If they kill us, we die; if they don't kill us, we live".
She said while she was thinking about going back to the man
to collect the sum of N400,000 to sell her son to the man,
a woman met her who had been assisting her, giving her food.
She asked, "Why are you crying? What is the problem?"
She said, "Look, I met a man who wants to buy my son for N400,000 so I could pay my debt".
The woman told her, "No, you dont need to do that. I'm going to assist you,
give you some money so that you can travel down to Lagos".
When I was leaving at 2 am, I woke up these children.
I brought some cheap plastic bags and put their clothes in before we left.
We started at 2 AM and crossed a bridge.
That day, I thought we would die.
When we got to Osarame Park, I cried out.
The manager asked me, "Madam, what brought you here this early morning?"
I started crying and told him I was on the run
and that I owed debts from my head to my toes.
I told him that I wanted to sell my child.
He said, "No, just run to The SCOAN and that God would answer you".
After that, the man booked tickets for me to get here for free.
She said that after she left at midnight because she thought
the people she was owing money to would arrest her or think she was running away,
The woman told her, "Look, very early morning go to the park".
When she got to the park, she didn't have money to travel on the bus to Lagos.
That was how she met the manager of the transport company.
The man asked her, "Madam, why are you standing here with these little children at this hour?"
She told the man, "Look, I'm about to sell my child for N400,000".
The man said, "No, you don't need to do that.
Enter the bus for free and travel down to Lagos".
And that's how she came down to The SCOAN.
Since she has been delivered, these children need to be given scholarship.
Also, we are to give her N400,000 so she can pay her debts.
And give them 5 bags of rice.
This is what my whole family could not pay.
For the rest of my life, they could not pay this money.
I want to challenge the congregation to come together.
Apart from this N400,000, contribute at least N100,000 for her to continue her business.
This money is to pay the debts.
Five bags of rice and scholarships - the church will give that.
We should come together and give another N100,000 for her to start her business.
Thank You, Jesus!
I thank the man of God for what he has done for me.
My whole generation could not pay. My brothers and sisters could not pay.
I thank God for today!
Help me thank God and the man of God.
We have people like this in the society.
If these children are not cared for, they will become another thing in the future.
What can we do for you, sir?
I came from Warri too. I want to assist her with N100,000.
You want to give her N100,000?
Yes.
Thank you.
Can you see what I'm talking about?
Many who are here today are crying in their spirit and soul.
They know they can do better than what they are doing.
Look at this woman from Warri.
We have people here from the Eastern communities to this place who are millionaires
but they cannot help her.
They keep helping others who will say, "Thank you"
because they have nothing to gain from this woman.
She's not a young lady; they cannot go out with her.
She has children; they cannot marry her.
There's nothing you can do; she will become a burden to them.
You can't put her in your office to be your clerk or manager.
You can't send her on any errand. So they feel helping her is of no use.
These are the kind of people you should raise.
We come from different backgrounds.
Today is Sunday; yesterday was Saturday.
Many came from parties where they danced and displayed money.
Many from clubs - social clubs, community clubs, different backgrounds.
Many went to weddings yesterday, or funerals.
In those places, they displayed money; they showed off money.
But here is the house of God.
Why can't we let the world know the value of money?
The real value of money is to help our fellow brothers.
You are blessed to bless others.
That is the real value.
The real value is to help the needy.
You are because I am; I am because you are.
Where I'm weak, you are strong; where I'm strong, you are weak.
So what we are doing now is to tell you that,
when you leave here today,
don't let your fellow brother come to you and say, "I need your help".
Even at the house where you are living,
how can you see little children on Monday, Tuesday roaming about?
And you cannot ask them, "Are you not going to school?
What are you doing at home?"
By the time you meet the parents, they will tell you,
"We are very sorry, we cannot afford the school fees".
Come to their aid.
In many homes you are living in,
every day, the tenants fight with the landlords.
You always hear their voices.
Why can't you come to their aid and ask the landlord what the problem is.
The landlord would say, "The problem is that he refuses to pay house rent".
Why can't you call the tenant,
"What is the problem? Do you want to live here? How much do you need?"
Help; settle them down. Don't allow this marriage to lead to divorce.
Thank you.
The reason why we are doing this is to change your perception, belief and philosophy.
What you are used to is to give those who can give you, who appreciate you.
You love appreciation.
We just received a phone call on one of our prayer lines,
by one of the viewers who was watching Emmanuel TV
and he saw the woman, listened to her pathetic story,
the woman who was delivered from the spirit of credit
and the man of God blessed her with the sum of N400,000.
The man said he's ready to pay her house rent and take care of her for one whole year.
The SCOAN and Emmanuel TV cannot go anywhere without the ministry of giving.
And what are we giving?
Love, strength, faithfulness, kindness, goodness,
every good thing the Lord has given us, money.
That is another ministry.
We must give it unconditionally.
Your money must have a place it's going to to raise the standard of living for the glory of God.
Jesus came to restore the relationship and fellowship between God and man.
That is Christianity. It's all about relationship.
Tell you neighbour, "Christianity is all about relationship.
Jesus came to restore the relationship and fellowship between God and man".
My name is Esse, I came from Warri.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was the problem of credit.
I owed but could not pay.
When I came to The SCOAN, I was sitting inside the church.
When the wise men were coming, my body began to shake.
I didn't know what they carried in their hands that made me shake.
Before I knew it, I found myself in front of the altar.
The man of God was asking, "Where is the woman who owes debt?"
She said that when she came here, she had an encounter with Wise Man Racine,
and the evil spirit that was in her life, the spirit of credit, was provoked,
and she was delivered from that spirit of credit.
Since the deliverance that day, my body feels so light.
There was a huge man who used to come to my dreams.
The last time the man came, after sleeping with me,
he used a handkerchief to clean up my body.
The day the wise man delivered me, I felt so free; I slept like a baby.
Today when I told the man of God my problem, the man of God told me
he would give me money and give my children scholarships.
Today, the man of God gave me the sum of N400,000
and a member of the church gave me N100,000,
which is N500,000 and five bags of rice.
The Emmanuel TV team promised me an apartment and feeding for one year.
Thank You, Jesus Christ! What an incredible transformation
that is taking place in her life.
She said that when she came here, the man of God, T.B. Joshua,
gave her the sum of N400,000 to pay off her debt.
Not only that, a member of the congregation came out
and blessed her with the sum of N100,000
to combine it together to pay off all her debt as well.
Not only that, she was also blessed with scholarship for her children
Not only that, she was also blessed with scholarships for her children and five bags of rice.
And if that wasn't enough, a person called the Emmanuel TV prayer line
and said that they wanted to sponsor and pay for her accomodation - her rent for an entire year.
I feel so happy because my whole generation couldn't pay the money.
May God guide him and his family
and give him long life and prosperity.
We want to encourage you to make God's Word the standard for your lives
so that your source of income can continue to come from God Almighty,
and make Jesus Christ the boss, the CEO, the director of all you do in life.
As you do so, your way will be prosperous and successful.
Anything you put your hand to will be prosperous in Jesus' mighty name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.